== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Skype ringing)
(Amy(on Skype):)Hi, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Amy:)Are you feeling any better?
(Sheldon:)Physically, yes, but I'm upset
(Sheldon:)because everyone's mad at me
for no good reason.
(Amy:)Why don't you tell me
what happened,
(Amy:)and in a gentle, loving way,
(Amy:)I'll explain to you
why you're wrong.
(Sheldon:)You know how, when you're sick,
(Sheldon:)you're allowed to be cranky
and say whatever you want
(Sheldon:)and other people's feelings
don't matter?
(Amy:)Ooh. Gentle and loving...
this is gonna be tricky.
I had a 101 fever.
(Sheldon:)If that's not a time to verbally
abuse my loved ones, when is?
(Amy:)Sheldon, when you're sick,
you can be... unbearable.
(Amy:)That's why your friends
have been known
(Amy:)to work late
or sneak out to the movies
(Amy:)or stay at
a neurobiology conference
(Amy:)three days after it's ended.